PRIYANSHI GUPTA

priyanshi26feb@gmail.com | +91 8750457252 | LinkedIn

SUMMARY

Professional in project management with three years of experience executing projects ranging from EPC bulk material handling to automobile production. Certified Scrum Master, team player, and quick learner who is always motivated to learn new skills and solve challenges in innovative ways.

SKILLS

Project Management

Project Coordination & Documentation

Schedule Preparation

Capacity Planning

Supply Chain Mgt

Vendor Management

Scrum

Digital Transformation

Factory CAD/ AutoCAD

Hindi

English

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MARUTI SUZUKI INDIA LIMITED

Gurugram, India

Assistant Manager, New Projects Department, Production Vertical

May 2022 – Present

- Capacity Planning: Created five year production plan for Engine and Transmission plants based on sales projections (~33 Lakhs/units per annum); Helped to identify shortfalls and plan out strategies for optimization
- **Digital Transformation:** Leading a team of 3 for developing 3D models of the production facilities from 2D layouts and visualized them using virtual reality for interference analysis.
- **Project Management:** Managing end-to-end production facility development projects of 2 new upcoming major models, overseeing project timelines, budgets, and incorporation of production requirements in new model design
- Coordinated cross-functional teams for CAD Data analysis of product design to identify defects and production feasibility
- Leading day-wise schedule preparation on monthly rolling plan basis for all upcoming model trials
- Contributed to manpower development by providing hands-on training to employees on schedule preparation and monitoring

ISGEC HEAVY ENGINEERING LIMITED

Project Engineer, Contracts Department, EPC Division

Noida, India Oct 2021 - May 2022

Graduate Engineer Trainee

Oct 2020- Sept 2021

- **Project Management:** Served as the primary contact between clients (Mahagenco and Vedanta Limited) and project teams, managing the execution of large-scale EPC turnkey projects related to bulk material handling worth value of ~INR 750 Cr
- Prepared project document, schedule in compliance with contract terms and billing plan; raising accurate billing to clients
- **Supply chain Management**: Managed technical discussions, manufacturing follow-ups, quality inspections with various vendors for delivery of mechanical, electrical and instrumentation items on site
- Initiated & developed "Risk & Opportunity Register"; improved timely delivery from 80% to 90% and reduced CoPQ by 4%
- Conducted a successful 5S Audit in the department resulting in a 50% increase in employee efficiency

DELHI METRO RAIL CORPORATION LIMITED

Summer Intern, Brakes & Pneumatic Department

Delhi, India Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

• Conducted in-depth research on the car body, brakes, and pneumatic system of a metro car

FLOWMORE LIMITED

Delhi, India Jun 2018 - Jul 2018

Summer Intern, Assembly and Quality Check Department
Studied assembly procedures & quality check tests of vertical turbine pumps

EDUCATION

INDIRA GANDHI DELHI TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY FOR WOMEN

Delhi, India

B. Tech - Mechanical & Automation Engineering

77.24%

Aug 2016 – May 2020

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES

• Certified Scrum Master from Scrum Alliance

Apr 2023

CERTIFICATE COURSES

Completed Data Driven Supply Chain Transformation course from IIM Mumbai (formerly NITIE).

Aug 2023 Jun 2023

Completed Excel Fundamentals for Data Analysis course from Coursera
 Completed Fundamental of Digital Marketing course from Google Digital Garage

Feb 2023

Completed courses in Pricing Strategy & Negotiation Skills (Apr 2023); Corporate Strategy (Jan 2023); Business Analytics Fundamentals (Oct 2022); Microsoft Projects (Apr 2022); and Project Management (Jun 2021) from Udemy
 2021-2023

Completed Diploma in Mechanical CAD.

Apr 2018

PUBLICATIONS

- Green operations management for sustainable development: An explicit analysis using fuzzy best-worst method (<u>link</u>) **Jan 2022**
- Evaluation of green operations management by fuzzy analytical hierarchy process: Presented the paper in FLAME 2020 conference (link)

 Aug 2020